Guide to the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBCJA), Local 132 Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBCJA), Local 132 archives
- Membership Files, 1910-2007 and undated; 11.50 linear feet
  - Membership Files -- Day Book, June 1974 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Dues, 2001-2007 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Dues, 2001-2007 (Box 46, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Dues, 2001-2007 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Dues, 2001-2007 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Miscellaneous, 1938-1943, 1967 and undated (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Officers and Trustees Meeting Night -- Signatures, 1977-1983 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Roll Call Book, 1934-1938 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Roll Call Book, 1984-1989 (Folder 7.0)
  - Membership Files -- Roll Call Book, 1990-1996 (Folder 8.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 7.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 8.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 9.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 10.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 11.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 12.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 13.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 14.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 15.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 16.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 17.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 18.0)
  - Membership Files -- Suspended Books, 1994 (Folder 19.0)
- Publications, 1912-1998; 0.25 linear feet
  - Publications -- AFL-CIO -- "The Builders", 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 1.0)
  - Publications -- Agreements, 1981 (Folder 2.0)
  - Publications -- Carpenter's News, 1970-1980 (Folder 3.0)
  - Publications -- Convention Files -- Seventeenth Biennial (cover only), 1912 (Folder 4.0)
  - Publications -- Labor-Management Reporting & Disclosure Act of 1959 (Folder 5.0)
  - Publications -- Sawing Through, 1973-1982 (Folder 6.0)
  - Publications -- The Thalco Trainer for Stewards & Committeemen, 1970 (Folder 7.0)
  - Publications -- Washington Building Trades Journal, 1947 (Folder 8.0)
- Contractor Files, 1977-1999 and undated; 1.75 linear feet
  - Contractor Files -- Absolute Fixture Services, 1994-1995 (Folder 9.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Active Negotations -- Hyatt Regency Hotel, 1989-1990 (Folder 10.0)
  - Contractor Files -- ACE Scaffolding, 1977 (Folder 11.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Barianos Historic Restoration, January 29, 1988 (Folder 12.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Blazer Enterprises, July 11, 1998 (Folder 13.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Boscart Construction, 1994-1996 (Folder 14.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Catalytic Enterprises Limited, 1989-1993 (Folder 15.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Chas H. Riddle Company, 1993 (Folder 16.0)
  - Contractor Files -- CHC Contracting -- Grievances, 1995 (Folder 17.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Chopp and Company, 1990 (Folder 18.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Chopp and Company -- Agreement, March 26, 1990 (Folder 19.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Chopp and Company -- Agreements, 1990 (Folder 20.0)
  - Contractor Files -- C.J. Coakley Company, 1988-1992 (Box 49, Folder 1.0)
  - Contractor Files -- C.J. Coakley Company, 1993-1998 (Folder 2.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Coastal Marine Science, 1998 (Folder 3.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1978-1979 and undated (Folder 4.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Collective Bargaining Agreement -- Study, September 20, 1993 (Folder 5.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Commerical Interiors, February 27, 1998 (Folder 6.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Contract Negotiations Exhibit Aid, 1989 (Folder 7.0)
  - Contractor Files -- D and D Project Expeditors, April 1997 (Folder 8.0)
  - Contractor Files -- DMP Contractors Inc., August 31, 1994 (Folder 9.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Drywall Contractors Meeting, 1989-1990 (Folder 10.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Eagle Corporation (The), 1994-1995 (Folder 11.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Exhibit - Aids of Maryland Inc., 1987-1990 (Folder 12.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Financial Core Membership -- Letters, 1988-1990 (Folder 13.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Galbreath Company -- Contract Negotiations, 1990-1991 (Folder 14.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Galbreath Company -- Wage Negotiations, 1990-1992 (Folder 15.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Galbreath-Ruffin Corp. -- Agreements, 1989 (Folder 16.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Galbreath-Ruffin Corp. -- Wage Negotiations, 1989-1990 (Folder 17.0)
  - Contractor Files -- George Hyman Construction Co., 1988-1996 (Folder 18.0)
  - Contractor Files -- George Hyman Construction Co. -- Contract Negotations, 1988 (Folder 19.0)
  - Contractor Files -- George Hyman Construction Co. -- Missing Tools, September 1991 (Folder 20.0)
  - Contractor Files -- George Hyman Construction Co. -- Project Agreements, December 1991 (Folder 21.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Hope Properties, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 1.0)
  - Contractor Files -- J.D. Allen Company, 1989-1990 (Folder 2.0)
  - Contractor Files -- LTI Contracting/Low Temp Insulations, Inc., R.J. Industries Inc., October 15, 1997 (Folder 3.0)
  - Contractor Files -- LCB Services, Inc., August 11, 1999 (Folder 4.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Maryland Drywall, 1988 (Folder 5.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Maryland Wood Preserving Corporation, 1989-1990 (Folder 6.0)
  - Contractor Files -- May Department Stores Company, December 18, 1998 (Folder 7.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Mid-Atlantic Laboratory Fixtures Inc., 1990 (Folder 8.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Minority Contractors, undated (Folder 9.0)
  - Contractor Files -- M.J. Fernandez Co. Inc., September 17, 1991 (Folder 10.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Nondiscrimination, 1984-1996 (Folder 11.0)
  - Contractor Files -- OMNI Shoreham Hotel, 1988-1999 (Folder 12.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Pittcon Industries, 1987-1988 (Folder 13.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Pittcon Industries, 1987-1988 (Folder 14.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Professional Installations, Inc., 1996 (Folder 15.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Rayman, Martin and Fader Inc. -- Bad Checks, 1992-1993 (Folder 16.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Rayman, Martin and Fader Inc. -- Bankruptcy, 1992-1993 (Folder 17.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Riggs Distler and Co. Inc., 1987-1996 (Folder 18.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Southeastern Floor Co., 1992 (Folder 19.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Southern Pan and Shoring -- Federal Triangle, 1994-1995 (Folder 20.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Southern Pan and Shoring -- Grievance, September 1994 (Folder 21.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Standard Acoustics Inc./Ceilings and Partitions Inc., 1988-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Underpinning and Foundation Constructors, Inc., October 1997 (Folder 2.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Union Bid List, undated (Folder 3.0)
  - Contractor Files -- VCI, Inc., November 18, 1997 (Folder 4.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Volpe Construction Co. Inc., September 16, 1988 (Folder 5.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Woods, Susan Inc. -- Trust Fund Purposes Only, 1993-1999 (Folder 6.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Woods, Susan Inc./KWK, 1992-1999 (Folder 7.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Woods, Susan Inc./KWK, 1994-1995 (Folder 8.0)
  - Contractor Files -- W. S. Schlosser Co. Inc., 1989-1992 (Folder 9.0)
  - Contractor Files -- Ziniz Inc., June 1990 (Folder 10.0)
- Photographs, 1900 and 1998; 1.50 linear feet and 1 item
  - Photographs -- Pins and Certificates, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 1.0)
  - Photographs -- 20th General Convention, 1900 (Box 53, Folder 1.0)
- Memorabilia, 1950 and undated; 4 items
  - Memorabilia (2468) -- Resolution regarding Joseph K. Potter, undated (Box 54, Folder 1.0)
  - Memorabilia (2469) -- Embossing Stamp, undated (Box 55, Folder 1.0)
  - Memorabilia (2470) -- Kaiser Steel, 1950 (Folder 2.0)
  - Memorabilia (2558) -- Local 132 T-shirt, undated (Folder 3.0)